Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845-1993 MSS.057
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence, 109217
  - Subseries 1B: Correspondence to Charles L. Dodgson, 109234
    - Salisbury, Lady Georgina to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p 20 Arlington Street, S.W., [May] 11, [n.y.] (XV 269)Marked "82590" 7 x 9, [1893]; 2210; 109250 (Box 5, Folder 451)
    - Taylor, H. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp The Uplands, East [Sheen], September 1, 1862 (XV 237) 7 x 9, 2211; 109249 (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, April 4, [n.y.] (XV 283) 7 x 9, undated; 109248 (Box 5, Folder 452.A)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., July 22, 1890, [ (XV 284) 7 x 4.5, 109247 (Box 5, Folder 452.B)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., July 4, 1893 (XV 285) 7 x 4.5, 109246 (Box 5, Folder 452.C)
    - Tenniel, Sir John to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1pp Portsdown Road, Maida Hill W., September 9, 1896 (XV 286) 7 x 9, 109245 (Box 5, Folder 452)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp 33 Longridge Road, South Kensington, March 15, 1883 (XV 292) Marked "42712". 6 x 8, 2215; 109244 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 4pp Tuesday [n.p., n.d.] (XV 293) Marked "42081". 7 x 9, undated; 2219; 109243 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Ellen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 5pp The Crown Hotel, Seven Oaks, May 26, 1884 (XV 294)Both sheets marked "47109". 7 x 4.5, 2224; 109242 (Box 5, Folder 453)
    - Terry, Kathleen to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp [n.p.] Saturday, June 8, 1868 (XV 239) 7 x 9, 2230; 109241 (Box 5, Folder 454)
    - Watts, G.F. to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Little Holland House, July 15, 1864 (XV 258) 8.25 x 5.25, 2233; 109240 (Box 5, Folder 455)
    - Yates, Edmund to Dodgson, Charles ANs, 1p 3 Abbey Road, St. John"s Wood, N.W. (XV 233) 7 x 4.5, undated; 2236; 109239 (Box 5, Folder 456)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 2pp Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, February 23, 1878 (XV 254) Marked "26661" 7 x 9, 2237; 109238 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, January 15, 1880 (XV 255). 5.5 x 7.25, 2240; 109237 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 1p Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, May [15][n.y.] (XV 256) Marked "36749". 7.25 x 4.5, [1881]; 2241; 109236 (Box 5, Folder 457)
    - Yonge, Charlotte to Dodgson, Charles ALs, 3pp Elderfield, Otterbourne, Winchester, December [30, n.y.]] (XV 257) "Marked 85573". 5.5 x 3.5, 1893; 2242; 109235 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Subseries 1C: Other Contemporary Correspondence., 109224
    - De La Mare, Walter to Shawyer, Mrs. TLs, 1p Hill House, Taplow, Buckinghamshire, September 27, 1932 (XII 218) See Manuscripts File:., 109233 (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - De La Mare, Walter to Shawyer, Mrs. TLs, 1p Hill House, Taplow, Buckinghamshire, October 27, 1932 (XII 219) See manuscript file titled Miscellaneous Memoirs of Charles Dodgson., 109232 (Box 5, Folder 458)
    - Dodgson, Menella to Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 17, 1898 (XIII 207), 109231 (Box 5, Folder 459)
    - Dodgson, Wilfred to Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 5, 1898 (XIII 207) With envelope. See picture file: Stevens, 109230 (Box 5, Folder 460)
    - Furniss, Harry to Edward Russell ALs, illus, 1p 23 St. Edmund"s Terrace, Regent"s Park, N.W., August 5, 1885., 109229 (Box 5, Folder 461)
    - Furniss, Harry to Edward Russell ALs, illus, 1p Garrick Club, January 28, 1902., 109228 (Box 5, Folder 462)
    - Maitland, Alice to [Rees, Reverend A. Williams] ALs, 8pp 1 Chatsworth Villas, Old Bath Road, Cheltenham, February 8, 1899 (XVI 295)With envelope. See manuscript file titled Miscellaneous Memoirs of Charles Dodgson., 109227 (Box 5, Folder 463)
    - Terry, Ellen to Rix, Lottie ALs, 2pp [22 Barkston Gardens, Earls Court, S.W., December 20, 1892]., 109226 (Box 5, Folder 464)
    - Terry, Ellen to Rix, Mrs. ALs, 2pp 22 Barkston Gardens, Earls Court, S.W., January 11, 1893., 109225 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - Subseries 1D: Calling Cards, 109218
    - Ruskin, John Calling Card Denmark Hill "John Ruskin" With penciled notes., undated; 109223 (Box 5, Folder 465)
    - Ruskin, John Card "Mr Ruskin"s,/Tea and Coffee Shop/.."., undated; 109222 (Box 5, Folder 466)
    - Ruskin, Mrs. Calling Card "Mrs Ruskin" Black border., undated; 109221 (Box 5, Folder 467)
    - Ruskin, Mrs. Calling Card "Mrs Ruskin" Black border., undated; 109220 (Box 5, Folder 468)
    - Watson, Lady Calling Card Peacehaven, Sussex "Lady Watson" With penciled note, undated; 109219 (Box 5, Folder 469)
- Series 2: Manuscripts, 109164
  - Subseries 2A: Manuscripts by Charles L. Dodgson., 109172
    - Dodgson, Charles "A 12 fold Division of Magnitudes.. " Ms, 1p [Christ Church], Oxford, Nov 11, 1886 Christ Church Common Room Weekly Bill on verso. 5.75 x 11.25, 1703; 109216 (Box 6, Folder 470)
    - Dodgson, Charles Let q=.."" Ms, 2pp [Christ Church], [Oxford], [n.d.] (X148) Series of questions/theorems numbered with roman numerals ." 11.25 x 4.25, undated; 1706; 109215 (Box 6, Folder 471)
    - Dodgson, Charles "5329 Articles.." Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 552) A tally of sums. 8.75 x 12, undated; 1709; 109214 (Box 6, Folder 472)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Alice in Wonderland/A Dream Play/For Children" Ms, 1p [n.p.],[n.d.] (344) Title page mock up. 7.5 x 5, undated; 1710; 109213 (Box 6, Folder 473)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Arithmetical Croquet" Ms, 1p [n.p.],[n.d.] (XX 566). 7 x 9, undated; 1711; 109212 (Box 6, Folder 474)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Charade" Mss illus, 3pp [n.p.], April 8, 1878 (332)Cyclostyle. Inscribed "B.H. from C.L.D." Signed "Lewis Carroll"., 109211 (Box 6, Folder 475)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Charade" Mss illus, 3pp [n.p.], March 31, 1890 (333)Cyclostyle. Inscribed "Presented to Edith Blakemore/by the Author - Mar. 31, 1890." Cyclostyle drawings appended and modifed by Dodgson. Signed "Lewis Carroll" 8.75 x 11.25, 1716; 109210 (Box 6, Folder 476)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Declamation Read in Hall" Ms, 4pp [n.p.], May 3, 1854 (XIX 448) 9 x 14, 1719; 109209 (Box 6, Folder 477)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Dedicated to a tea-tea. Why? Oh when?" Mss, 1p [n.p.], March 16, 1880 (III 40) Acrostic originally send to Alexandra Kitchin. Signed "Lewis Carroll". 9 x 7, 1724; 109208 (Box 6, Folder 478)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A Dream Cast" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (345) Cast list for Saville-Clark play. 9 x 5.5, undated; 1725; 109207 (Box 6, Folder 479)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae [Group C.]" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], March 11, 1878. 9 x 11, 1728; 109206 (Box 6, Folder 480)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae [Group C.]" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], March 11, 1878 Not hand written. Printed with holograph corrections. 9 x 11, 1732; 109205 (Box 6, Folder 481)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Formulae F" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] Portion of document pasted on cardboard backing., undated; 109204 (Box 6, Folder 482)
    - Dodgson, Charles "The Four Syllogisms" Ms, 1p [n.p.], November 27, 1887. 9 x 11, 1736; 109203 (Box 6, Folder 483)
    - Dodgson, Charles "To Hallie" Ms, 3pp [n.p.], November, 1868 (II 31)Inscribed to Clara Cunnynghame 6 x 7.75, 1737; 109202 (Box 6, Folder 484)
    - Dodgson, Charles "The Hunting of the Snark" Ms, 1p [n.p.], February 17, 1889 (XIX 523)Holograph draft of advertisement text. 3.25 x 7, 1741; 109201 (Box 6, Folder 485)
    - Dodgson, Charles "I sent off your promised fountain pen... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (IV 83) Text fragment. 1.75 x 4.5, undated; 1742; 109200 (Box 6, Folder 486)
    - Dodgson, Charles "La Guida di Bragia" Ms, 14 leaves bound in paper wrapper [n.p.], [n.d.] With correspondence and a typed copy of the play. 8.5 x 14, undated; 1745; 109199 (Box 6, Folder 487)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Let AB, CD be such Lines " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (X 152) Mathematical notes. 11 x 9, undated; 1773; 109198 (Box 6, Folder 488)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Logic Analytical" Ms illus, 1pp [n.p.], November 21-22, 1894 (IV 83) Mathematical and/or logical diagram. Christ Church Junior Common Room account form on verso. 10.25 x 8.25, 1776; 109197 (Box 6, Folder 489)
    - Dodgson, Charles "A master of a man"s parent is that man"s superior " Ms, 1p [n.p.], March 5, 1897 (XIX 563) Originally written to Louisa Dodgson. Logic problem. 4.25 x 7, 1779; 109196 (Box 6, Folder 490)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Miss M. Cunnynghame, Debtor to Mr. C.L. Dodgson" Mss, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 33) A mock bill. 5.5 x 8, undated; 1780; 109195 (Box 6, Folder 491)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first"s a drink resembling wine " Ms, 1p [n.p.], February 23, 1880 (III 42)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin 4.75 x 7, 1783; 109194 (Box 6, Folder 492)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first has no beard... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (III 42)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin. 5 x 8, undated; 1784; 109193 (Box 6, Folder 493)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first turns cows to solitary birds... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (III 41)Acrostic originally sent to Alexandra Kitchin. 8 x 6, undated; 1785; 109192 (Box 6, Folder 494)
    - Dodgson, Charles "My first we call here when her belt is on... " Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (IV 83) Cartoons removed to picture file. Pencil on fragment of paper. 2.5 x 4, undated; 1786; 109191 (Box 6, Folder 495)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Name, Information required" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], March 17, 1887 (346) Cast list for Saville-Clark play. 11.25 x 9, 1787; 109190 (Box 6, Folder 496)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Nella"s song" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 474a) Originally written for [Menella Wilcox] On cardboard backing. 7 x 4.5, undated; 1790; 109189 (Box 6, Folder 497)
    - Dodgson, Charles "No, no! I cannot write a line,... " Ms, 1pp [n.p.], April 10, 1871 (II 32) Verses originally written for Margaret Cunnynghame. Poem in hand not Dodgson"s on verso.. 7 x 6.75, 1793; 109188 (Box 6, Folder 498)
    - Dodgson, Charles "N.S. Began Sep. 14/1752" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], March 3, 1887 (X 144). 7 x 9, 1796; 109187 (Box 6, Folder 499)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Questions III" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.] 9 x 5.75, undated; 1797; 109186 (Box 6, Folder 500)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Questions IV" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], [n.d.]. 5 x 8, undated; 1798; 109185 (Box 6, Folder 501)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Symbols for properties for a pair of Lines" Ms, 1p [n.p.], April 2, 1878. 11 x 9, 1799; 109184 (Box 6, Folder 502)
    - Dodgson, Charles "There are certain conditions... " Ms, 1p [n.p.], March 23, 1893 (X 137) 8.75 x 6, 1800; 109183 (Box 6, Folder 503)
    - [Digital image with no corresponding folder], undated; 1457; 109182 (Box 6, Folder ID: 503.1)
    - Dodgson, Charles "There is this difference" Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (XIX 449) 8 x 12.5, undated; 1801; 109181 (Box 6, Folder 504)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], October 31, 1886 (343) 9 x 7, 1806; 109180 (Box 6, Folder 505)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (342) [--551 in DB?--]. 4.5 x 7, undated; 1807; 109179 (Box 6, Folder 506)
    - Dodgson, Charles ""Tis the Voice of the Lobster" Ms, 1p [n.p.], [n.d.] (342) [--551 in DB?--]., undated; 2246; 109178 (Box 6, Folder 506)
    - Dodgson, Charles Useful and Instructive Poetry Ms, illus, 42 leaves bound in boards [Croft], 1845., 1811; 109177 (Box 6, Folder ID: 506.1)
    - Dodgson, Charles "To Dine if I come in a queer way" Ms, 1pp [n.p.], October 31, 1886 (551) Sent to Edith Lucy. 4.25 x 9, 1808; 109176 (Box 6, Folder 507)
    - Dodgson, Charles "What Tottles Meant" Ms, 4pp [n.p.], [n.d.] 9 x 5.5, undated; 1890; 109175 (Box 6, Folder 508)
    - Dodgson, Charles [Word Game] Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 30) Sent to Margaret Cunnynghame. 4.5 x 7, undated; 1895; 109174 (Box 6, Folder 509)
    - Dodgson, Charles [Word Game] Ms, 2pp [n.p.], [n.d.] (II 36) Sent to Margaret Cunnynghame. 1.5 x 3.5, undated; 1899; 109173 (Box 6, Folder 510)
  - Subseries 2B: Corrected Proofs, 109170
    - Dodgson, Charles Curiosissima Curatoria Ms corrected proof sheets 4 folded signatures, dated and numbered [n.p.], August 10. 1892 4 folded signatures. Signature A is numbered 79366, B & C 79109, and D 79276. 7.5 x 5, undated; 1902; 109171 (Box 6, Folder 511)
  - Subseries 2C: Manuscripts by others., 109165
    - Lord Simon [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ts, 12pp [n.p.], [n.d.] Document contains both typescript and holograph pages., undated; 109169 (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Waterhouse, Mrs. A.T. [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ms, 7pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated; 109168 (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Rowell, Mrs. H.L. [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ms, 6pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated; 109167 (Box 6, Folder 512)
    - Davies, Mrs. Arthur [Memoir of Charles Dodgson] Ts, 3pp [n.p.], [n.d.]., undated; 109166 (Box 6, Folder 512)
- Series 3: Drawings, 109125
  - Subseries 3A: Drawings by Charles L. Dodgson, 109151
    - Dodgson, Charles "Copied from Wilkinson"s "Manners and Customs of the Ancient Egyptians" Vol II, pp. 18, 57" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]. 5.5 x 8.75, undated; 1908; 109163 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Edith" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 (VI 107)Purple ink. 8.5 x 5.5, 1909; 109162 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - Dodgson, Charles "For Ina" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.]. 11 x 8.5, undated; 1910; 109161 (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Scene from the Burlesque of "Norma" acted at the Haymarket" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 11 x 8.5, 1911; 109160 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - Dodgson, Charles "Sketch from the Concert Room at St. Lenards" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], April 10, 1868 (I 6) in pencil on verso. 4.5 x 2.5, 1912; 109159 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], September 14, 1880 Classical Scene. Three figures, two dogs. 7.25 x 4.75, 1913; 109158 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawings, 2pp, pen and ink [n.p.], October 8, 1875 (IV 83) Cartoons. Purple ink. Done for Gertrude Chataway.. 8.75 x 7, 1914; 109157 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled [n.p.], [n.d.] Man with Axe. 7 x 4.5, undated; 1919; 109156 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] (I 1) Russian Drawings. Multiple heads and Russian annotations. Holograph on verso.. 7.25 x 4.5, undated; 1920; 109155 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] Russian Drawings. Four figures and Russian annotation. 2.5 x 4.5, undated; 1923; 109154 (Box 7, Folder 522)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [Christ Church, Oxford], [Jan 30, 1868] Self Portrait of Dodgson Lecturing. See Margaret Cunnynghame correspondence. 558 in blue and 671 on verso. 4 x 2.5, 1924; 109153 (Box 7, Folder 523)
    - Dodgson, Charles Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] [Tweedle Dee and Tweedle Dum] 7 x 4.5, undated; 1925; 109152 (Box 7, Folder 524)
  - Subseries 3B: Drawings by others, 109126
    - Furniss, Harry "Alice getting smaller..." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109150 (Box 7, Folder 525)
    - Furniss, Harry "Alice growing..." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109149 (Box 7, Folder 526)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Baby Kind" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908] Possibly a proof Sylvie and Bruno Concluded, undated; 109148 (Box 7, Folder 527)
    - Furniss, Harry "Down, down, down" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109147 (Box 7, Folder 528)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Gryphon and the Mock Turtle Dance" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109146 (Box 7, Folder 529)
    - Furniss, Harry "If you Please Sir" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109145 (Box 7, Folder 530)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Knave was standing between them..." Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109144 (Box 7, Folder 531)
    - Furniss, Harry "Lewis Carroll at the Play". Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] Figures and "by H. Furniss" on verso, undated; 109143 (Box 7, Folder 532)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mad Hatter"s Song" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109142 (Box 7, Folder 533)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mad Tea Party" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109141 (Box 7, Folder 534)
    - Furniss, Harry "The March Hare took the Watch and Dipped it Into a Cup of Tea" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109140 (Box 7, Folder 535)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Mock Turtle"s Song" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109139 (Box 7, Folder 536)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Pool of Tears" Drawing [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109138 (Box 7, Folder 537)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Queen of Hearts" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109137 (Box 7, Folder 538)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Queer Cocktail Party", depicts the mouse's tale Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109136 (Box 7, Folder 539)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Trial Scene" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109135 (Box 7, Folder 540)
    - Furniss, Harry "The Whole Pack Rose in the Air" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109134 (Box 7, Folder 541)
    - Furniss, Harry "The White Rabbit" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [1908], undated; 109133 (Box 7, Folder 541a.)
    - Furniss, Harry "What Tottles Meant" Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.] From Sylvie and Bruno Concluded, undated; 109132 (Box 7, Folder 542)
    - Rackham, Arthur Untitled Sketchbook for Rackham's 1907 Alice in Wonderland [n.p.] [1907], undated; 109131 (Box 7, Folder 543)
    - [Tenniel, John] Untitled Drawing [n.p.], [n.d.] Depiction of the caucus race. Inscribed "From [T] with love 1866", undated; 109130 (Box 7, Folder 544)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.], undated; 109129 (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.], undated; 109128 (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Tenniel, John Untitled Drawing, pen and ink [n.p.], [n.d.], undated; 109127 (Box 7, Folder 545)
- Series 4: Photographs, 109045
  - Subseries 4A: Photographs by Charles L. Dodgson., 109056
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Chataway, Gertrude Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2453. [n.p.][n.d.] Legs crossed. Bathing attire. Cap. On verso "2453" and "IV 44". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1926; 109124 (Box 7, Folder 546)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Dr.Robinson"s Class in Dr. Lee"s Museum Contemporary Photographic Print, [n.n.] [n.p.] [1858] Tipped into Fale"s copy 1 of De la Mare"s 1932 Lewis Carroll. Four men examining an animal skeleton., undated; 109123 (Box 7, Folder 546.1 tipped into book)
    - [Dodgson, Charles] Photo of Wilfred Dodgson Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.n], Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Seated in chair. Numbered II 37. Inscribed "Clara H. Cunningham/from Wilfred L. Dodgson". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1929; 109122 (Box 7, Folder 547)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Ffoulkes, [?] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2644, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Portrait of girl. Numbered on verso "2644", originally enclosed with letter XIX 472 to Mrs. Ffoulkes. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1932; 109121 (Box 7, Folder 548)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of[Kitchin, Alexandra] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2012, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Sitting in chair. Numbered "2012" on verso. Also, and probably mistakenly, labeled "Liddell" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1935; 109120 (Box 7, Folder 549)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2032, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] In chair holding box. Numbered on verso "2032". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1938; 109119 (Box 7, Folder 550)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Wearing coat and hat. Numbered "2132" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1941; 109118 (Box 7, Folder 551)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print [2143], Negative Number, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Inscribed in pencil "X by Mr. Dodgson." In beach attire with shovel and bucket. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1944; 109117 (Box 7, Folder 552)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [2155] [n.p.][n.d.] In Asian kimono with fan. No number. On verso "For Herbert Kitchin /from Lewis Carroll/Sept. 10 1873". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1947; 109116 (Box 7, Folder 553)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2251, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Leaning on pillow with left arm. Numbered "2251" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1950; 109115 (Box 7, Folder 554)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra [n.p.][n.d.] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2316, Mounted on Pasteboard In a crown and costume with leopard skin. Numbered on verso "2316". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1953; 109114 (Box 7, Folder 555)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra [n.p.][n.d.] Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2425, Mounted on Pasteboard In dress with sash, with violin. Numbered "2425" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1956; 109113 (Box 7, Folder 556)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2477, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] In dress with lace. numbered on verso "2477". 4 x 2.5, undated; 1959; 109112 (Box 7, Folder 557)
    - Dodgson, Charles Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2541, Mounted on Pasteboard Sitting on chair reading book. Numbered "2541" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1962; 109111 (Box 7, Folder 558)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2542, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] With violin standing next to chair. Numbered "2542" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1965; 109110 (Box 7, Folder 559)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number [n.p.][n.d.] In turban with fan. Numbered "2544" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1968; 109109 (Box 7, Folder 560)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook Contemporary Photographic Print,Negative Number 2316, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Full length figure of child on toy horse. Numbered on verso "2316". Note that there is another Dodgson of Alexandra Kitchin with the same number. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1971; 109108 (Box 7, Folder 561)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Brook Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2318, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] 3/4 length figure of child with mustache and costume. Numbered on verso "2318".) 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1974; 109107 (Box 7, Folder 562)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, George Herbert Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2141, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. Full length figure in jacket with frog fastenings. Numbered "2141" on verso. 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1977; 109106 (Box 7, Folder 563)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, George Herbert Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2142, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Mounted on pasteboard. 3/4 length figure in jacket with frog fastenings. Numbered in purple ink on verso in upper right corner"2134/ 2142.". 6.5 x 4.25, undated; 1980; 109105 (Box 7, Folder 564)
    - Dodgson, Charles Photo of Kitchin, Alexandra and Dorothy Contemporary Photographic Print, Negative Number 2641, Mounted on Pasteboard [n.p.][n.d.] Two girls together. Numbered "2641" on verso. 4 x 2.5, undated; 1983; 109104 (Box 7, Folder 565)